rcc.edu 2006-06-19

# Riverside Community College: Home Page

Riverside Community College (RCC) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information that you provide to us. The following statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use and disclosure of your personal information by RCC. Please note that, RCC reviews and updates this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how RCC collects and uses personal information. By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by RCC as explained below. 

  1. **Personal Information.**

You have complete control over your personal information. In general, you can visit our web site without providing us with any personal information. However, there are instances where we must have your personal information in order for us to grant you an access to our protected and secured sites. This information may include registration data (your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, title, etc.), information request data and response data ("User Information"). When you receive your confirmation email or when you receive any email from the list server, you will be given instructions on how to remove yourself from the list. 

  2. **Collection and Use of User Information.**

We intend to use information that you supply for purposes of supporting your relationship with RCC by designing content that is suitable to your needs and alerting you to news and information as they become available. 

RCC adheres strictly to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 please do not submit any User Information if you are less than 13 years of age.

  3. **Disclosure of User Information.**

RCC does not sell, trade or transfer User Information to third parties. However, we may share User Information within the confines of the various departments located within the district.

  4. **Accuracy and Security.**

The accuracy and security of the User Information is important to RCC. If you contact us to correct your User Information, we will attempt to correct such inaccuracies in a timely manner. RCC is concerned with the security of your User Information and is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect it from unauthorized access and use of that personal information. To that end, we put in place the appropriate physical, electronic and managerial policies and procedures to secure your personal User Information. We also continue to implement procedures to maintain accurate, complete and current User Information.

  5. **Usernames and Passwords.**

Access to certain content on our web site may be allowed under a written agreement between you and RCC and will require a username and/or password. In some cases, failure to provide personal information may prevent you from accessing certain RCC content containing certain confidential information, applications, or services. By accessing and using our protected and secured web site(s), you agree to maintain the confidentiality of the username and password you selected to access such site(s).

  6. **Cookies.**

RCC uses "cookies". A cookie is a small data file that a web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to keep records of the visits to such site. A cookie may contain information such as your IP address or browser that helps us recognize the pages you have visited and improve future visits, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is the information that you provide yourself. A cookie cannot read data off of your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. If you prefer not to accept a cookie, you can set your web browser to warn you before accepting cookies or you can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your web browser. However, access to our secured web site(s) may be hindered by such measures.

  7. **External Links.**

RCC provides links to other third party web sites. Even if the third party is affiliated with RCC, RCC is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk. 

  8. **General.**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please contact the webmaster. 

* * *

## Please update your browser

The browser you are using is incapable of viewing cascading style sheets (CSS) properly. In order to view this web site as it was intended, you should go to one of the following companies and download their most current web browser. 

  * Microsoft - [Internet Explorer](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/default.asp)
  * Netscape - [Navigator](http://channels.netscape.com/ns/browsers/download.jsp)
  * Opera - [ Opera Browser](http://www.opera.com/download/)
  * Freedom Scientific - [JAWS](http://www.freedomscientific.com/fs_downloads/index.asp) (Screen Reader)

If you believe that your browser is CSS-2 compliant and should view this page properly, please e-mail the webmaster the name and version of your browser as well as the operating system you are using so that we may be able to address the situation. Thank you for your assistance.
